smartvault.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy » SmartVault

SmartVault (“we” or “us”) values its users’ privacy. This privacy policy is effective June 2, 2011; it summarizes what information we might collect from a registered user or other visitor (“you”), and what we will and will not do with it. Please note that this privacy policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that SmartVault does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by SmartVault. If you visit a Web site that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information.

Notice to users in the European Union and Australia / New Zealand / Asia-Pacific

### What we do with your personally identifiable information

It is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services. “Personally identifiable information” means information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as, for example:

  * your name, company, email address, phone number, billing address, and shipping address
  * your SmartVault user ID and password
  * credit card information
  * any account-preference information you provide us
  * your computer’s domain name and IP address, indicating where your computer is located on the Internet
  * session data for your login session, so that our computer can ‘talk’ to yours while you are logged in.

If you do provide personally identifiable information to us, either directly or through a reseller or other business partner, we will:

  * not sell or rent it to a third party without your permission — although unless you opt out (see below), we may use your contact information to provide you with information we believe you need to know or may find useful, such as (for example) news about our services and products and modifications to the [Terms of Service](http://www.smartvault.com/company/terms-of-service.php "Terms of Service");
  * take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction;
  * not use or disclose the information except: 
    * as necessary to provide services or products you have ordered, such as (for example) by providing it to a carrier to deliver products you have ordered;
    * in other ways described in this privacy policy or to which you have otherwise consented;
    * in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined (for example, statistical compilations);
    * as required by law, for example, in response to a subpoena or search warrant;
    * to outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential;
    * as necessary to enforce the [Terms of Service](http://www.smartvault.com/company/terms-of-service.php "Terms of Service");
    * as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of SmartVault, its users, or others; this may include (for example) exchanging information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.

### Other information we collect

We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of our Web site(s); research and development; customer- and account administration; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely.

### Cookies

SmartVault uses “cookies” to store personal data on your computer. We may also link information stored on your computer in cookies with personal data about specific individuals stored on our servers. If you set up your Web browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Firefox) so that cookies are not allowed, you will not be able to use our Web site(s).

### External data storage sites

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

### Your privacy responsibilities

To help protect your privacy, be sure:

  * not to share your user ID or password with anyone else;
  * to log off the SmartVault Web site when you are finished;
  * to take customary precautions to guard against “malware” (viruses, Trojan horses, bots, etc.), by installing and updating commercially available anti-virus software.

### Notice to users in the European Union and Australia / New Zealand / Asia-Pacific

SmartVault’s operations are located primarily in the United States. If you provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of your home jurisdiction to the United States. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described in this privacy policy.

### Information collected from children

You must be at least 18 years old to use SmartVault’s Web site(s) and service(s). SmartVault does not knowingly collect information from children under 18. (See the [U.S.] Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.)

### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. We will notify you (by email to the email address you have provided) of any material change to how we will use personally identifiable information.

### Questions or comments?

If you have questions or comments about SmartVault’s privacy policy, send email to [support@smartvault.com](mailto:support@smartvault.com), or [contact us](http://www.smartvault.com/company/contactus.php "Contact Us").
